you want kappa two three
four
we put
six five seven six
two more 1 by 1 30 want to hold it for
10 days 10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 next wow
just keep it on
make sure it doesn't roll for
[Music]
three more create the low high
on last
130 water high one two three four five
six
but
2010 won we won jump we two
three
four
each other 25 pickups 26
28 - one way my last one go by 30 on all
its physical it's crazy four five six
seven eight nine ten
[Music]
three
four
[Music]
please
for let's invite to my birthday party
one two three four five five one three
six squad up we sound good okay
two more oh hi 99 one thirty one point
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten
very good next
yeah
looking around
below
the chin g20 last week
sixteen nice
6:18
this one's up high 20 Chuck 1 over 3 to
3 more white grease from a higher 3 for
just one if I hold it 1 2 3 4 5 6
8 9
but
[Music]
one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten